[{"answer": "We checked it out inside. Thought there might be a name or fingerprint somewhere. All we found was a curled page marking the fourteenth chapter of St. my friend's Revelations", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Maybe this is the teacher's edition", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Huh", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "It isn't so", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "How did I ever get you in my life", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "But I did it, didn't I? I did kill myself", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'll be okay", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I love you too, Jan", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Everyone did. He lived here", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "There are no secrets in small towns, Mr. my friend, dark or otherwise", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'm looking for something", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I will. Have you found what you're looking for", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "How did you end up a cop", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Are you always this cryptic", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I meant it as a compliment", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Goodnight, my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "And who did, my friend. Who talked to the man", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "And where is my friend, my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "She isn't here. She's sick", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "-- my friend", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " That's funny.", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It's all right, my friend. We know you love my friend..", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "She's going to have the Enemy Ghost Way. We leave this afternoon", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "In the home village. The Hand Trembler must have found corpse sickness..", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "She's already seen a doctor.  That son of a bitch..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "General my friend", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "He didn't like children", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I have faith in my friend. And that I'm going to save that little girl from those creeping things out there. From all of them", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Maybe we both were", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Just my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "He caught up with me", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Enemy Ghost Way for my friend", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah. Indian stuff", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Really", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "Prophecy_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yes, he was", "qsentId": 40}]